[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "If she is, will her parents ever find her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "It is wrong to give up on children who are still missing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Why have you done the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Of course my reason for writing it all down is quite different to the reason to publish it as a book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Gerry, obviously, that is the crux of this, isn't it, for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "To be here, years later, and have no idea where she is or what may have happened, it must be excruciating, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "It certainly was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "I mean, Kate, do you ever have a day where this doesn't consume you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "I don't think it consumes every minute as it did before.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Has that even entered your thought process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Or do you have to believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I don't think -- I don't think we can say 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Is that what you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "In terms of the normal practice, though, when you were with them, would you ever have left them alone in that situation if you'd been at home, for example, back in England?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Definitely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Another criticism as put to you is why didn't you just pay to have a nanny if you wanted to go out to dinner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Yes, I mean, it's not a question of money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Do you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, obviously, because of what's happened, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What was the exact moment -- let me ask you, Kate -- when you realized Madeleine had gone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, went back to do a check at 10:00 and I went through the patio doors at the back.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate", "Madeleine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "And what did you think in that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I thought someone's taken her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "You went down to tell Gerry straight away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gerry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "What are you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "The first thing that went straight through my head and I think -- it was just disbelief.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Do you know -- is there any evidence how this person came in the room?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I mean no doubt, there are a number of options.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "There's nothing they could find to say this is unequivocally how this person came in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Did that set alarm bells off when she did that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Well, it's one of those things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Now given the time that's gone past?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Have there been a number of burglaries there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "EX", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Do you know all the figures for that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "No, we're not sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Do you believe that if enough time and money and resources devoted to this, that there's some stone that's been left unturned in this investigation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "DT", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "I'm absolutely certain that there are things that could be done based on the information that's available to us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "What was the mood like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "The first police that turned up were what we call G&R police.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Did you think -- did you think, Gerry, from the start that they were suspicious of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Certainly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gerry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Has there been anything that if an outside lawyer looked at this, they would say, that doesn't add up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "You have to remember, there were nine people in the party here who didn't expect anything of this kind to happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 379, "question": "How did you manage to keep your composure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I think the key thing is -- I mean, as I say, behind the scenes --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Were you offered if you'd -- if you accept that you did this, you can go to prison for two years and be out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "It's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "That must have been a pretty awful experience, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "You know, it was a great story for the media.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "National Center for Missing"]}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJR", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Are there any that you think have any kind of credibility that you think should be really pushed further?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "It's incredibly difficult, Piers, because if you speak to -- here on in the island, the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children, who've got the most expertise in these types of stranger or stereotypical kidnappings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Do you think this could have split up many couples?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I think that's without doubt, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "I mean, at its worst, what's it been like trying to have a relationship through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "It's been incredibly difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Did either of you ever get suicidal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "How hard is it for you to see video footage of Madeleine, even now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I think it's the one medium that really brings her back to me, in particular, seeing her moving and her voice.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Madeleine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "What was that like for you, Kate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Well, at that point, it was just incredibly important.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "He just very simply took a photograph of Madeleine and placed his palm on it and blessed her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Has what's happened to you damaged your faith?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "It's challenged my faith.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Gerry, do you still keep Madeleine's room as it always was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Madeleine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "How have they dealt with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Brilliantly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What do they think happened to Madeleine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, they know that a man has taken her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "How do you deal with a birthday when she's not there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Well, what we've done the last few -- few years, we have marked the day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "If you're watching this interview and you're keen to try and help you in some way in the search for Madeleine, what is the most effective way that people can do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I think it's two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "And do you know if that would be still there if she's now eight years old?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Certainly believe it wouldn't have changed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "If people see somebody they think could possibly be Madeleine, who should they call?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "They should call the police, local police.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Have there been moments when you've been pretty much confident that you may have found her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "EX", "VBN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Do you still have any kind of conversation with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Can you sleep OK now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "I can, actually, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Do you think there's hope, or is it almost like a knife in your back that Madeleine hasn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I think, overall, it gives you hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Madeleine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Madeleine"]}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "If she was, what would you say to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I'd say, Madeleine, we're still looking for you and if you get a chance, tell the police who you are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Madeleine"]}, "docId": "110511pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "ORGAN: Kate, what would you -- what would you say, if you had the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I would just say, you know, we love you, Madeleine.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}]